I ate it like that, and it was really good.
Is it different from ordinary kikurage mushrooms?
Not at all. It's thicker.
They are mushrooms, right?
It's delivered live.
Yes, it is.
It was so delicious.
Well then, let's bring you another energetic delivery today.
Yes.
Kikurage is an interesting name, isn't it?
Like a jellyfish with writing on it.
You mean like a sea monster.
Oh, I see.
That's a hell of a sense of humor.
Oh!
Yoo-hoo!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Good evening. Good evening.
As usual, we'll be broadcasting live today.
I'd like to introduce you to some of the young people here at Ebichu.
Gandhani, Barikhata, and many others... they all have their own voice to greet you.
Gandanifire, balikata desu, and so on.
Don't you have something to say, too, Master?
Oh...
That's fine.
Snot!
That one, sure.
I said it! We were still discussing it!
But you're happy about it? Yes, I'm happy.
Pattern one. Pattern one.
What was that? Is there a pattern two?
Master.
Tightening? I see.
Like this.
There's no pattern 3, is there?
Master.
Oh!
Welcome.
He really was the third master, wasn't he?
Like, "Welcome.
Well, I have an announcement to make to all of you who are watching the live broadcast.
We will be doing it again this year, a special New Year's Eve live broadcast and live streaming of "Kanai Devil's New Year's Eve Live Broadcast!
This is Master!
Hello!
This year, we are going to broadcast a live New Year's Eve live broadcast from the Super Devil's Go Devil, the Devil who comes to the Super Devil's Go Devil.
We've been doing this every year, and we're going to do it again this year.
We will have a countdown from New Year's Eve to New Year's Day, and this will be the first time for me to do so.
It's amazing, isn't it, how everyone is so busy, even Ebichu is in different places, like they arrive by car and go right in. It was such a busy atmosphere.
Am I coming from NHK Hall? That's not true.
That's my dream. It's cool, isn't it? So, as for the content, well, it's the same as every year, you know.
I don't know, maybe a skit or something? I don't know.
I'm looking forward to bringing you another year's entertainment.
What do you think? I'd like to do something for Omisoh Day, and since it's so easy, I'd like to do something for the main event.
You want to do something?
I'm sure there are a lot of things you want to do.
You always break the Kagami... you know, Kagami-biraki? Kagamibiraki?
We used to do that.
We also made rice cakes.
I see.
She wants to try pounding rice cakes.
I'd like to try.
The real ones do it like this.
Like this.
I want to try it.
Sounds fun!
I'd like to try it.
They don't do that, do they?
Oh, flying... Oh, that's right.
We had a bungee jumping event.
But this year, you're going to do it?
What? I want to jump! I've never done it before.
Really? Are you sure you're okay with that?
No, it's...
Oh!
But I'd like to try it.
It's so sharp.
He wants to fly!
Well, some people are really special.
Thank you very much.
What? You're not good at it? I'm good at it.
I'm so good at it I can't even do bungee jumping.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, but if you do that, I'll have you skydiving.
But I'm sure skydiving will be fine... but I don't know what it's like when you're that high up...
But I wonder if skydiving is a breeze.
I don't know... the wind is blowing like a whirlwind.
And you probably wouldn't fly alone like that, would you?
Oh, that's right.
You'll be accompanied by a strong instructor, so you don't have to worry.
I guess so... They want me to fly like crazy.
They want me to fly, so... but, hypothetically speaking, what if New Chapter gets such an order? I want to do it! There he is! Kito's here, too!
We have a lot of challengers.
But I'm not sure I can fly.
I might get cold.
I understand that.
When you get to the top
Everyone who's ever done it says that.
But when you're up there and you have a little bit of time to think about it
I imagine all kinds of things, and I get scared.
I can't fly.
You should just say, "I've done it unexpectedly," and pretend that you're walking around.
You don't just walk away like that, you know, like you're just standing there and then you go...
I'm looking forward to it.
Well, there's still a little more time, isn't there?
Daikanai Deville will be held on Sunday, March 31st next year!
I've missed Taikanai. Yes, it's been a year since the first Taikanai Devil's Festival last year.
It's been a year since then.
And it's going to be held at the Kanagawa Prefectural Hall and the Kanagawa Prefectural Hall again.
I'm sure we'll have all kinds of interesting VTRs, skits, and other things like that, so please come and join us again next March 31st.
March 31 next year, that's pretty dramatic, isn't it?
March 31st is the last day of this fiscal year, isn't it?
By the way...
I've prepared some special seats for you.
We've prepared some special seats for you.
VIP seats.
The front of the line.
Right there.
You know...
Just now...
They just put up a website for applicants.
Will there be a lottery?
If you want to see it right in front of us, please apply.
There are special goods, and VIP special goods, and all kinds of other special offers.
If you want to see the show from the front...
If you want to see the show, you can apply now.
March, March, March!
We have Devil Stars.
Big Kannon Devil.
It's a commemoration of the "Big Kannon Devil" event.
Thank you very much. Tamamin gave me this.
Thank you, Tamamin. Thank you for the emo emo emo emo emo emo emo emo emo emo emo emo emo emo emo emo emo emo emo emo.
Takumi Minji Yes, congratulations on the decision to broadcast again this year.
Thank you very much for the special New Year's Eve live broadcast.
Thank you very much for your New Year's Eve live broadcast
I told you he was a snot... I don't know what kind of goods I'll be able to sell yet, but I'm sure I'll have a lot of things for you.
I don't know what kind of goods we can make yet, but there are various kinds of goods...
I'm going to sell some of my glassware.
I'm going to win that!
I'd like to sell some of your goods, but I'm not sure if I'd like to sell them here.
Thank you very much.
I heard you can go to the full-length version of the show, so please take a look.
So, that's all for now.
Now that that information is out...
Now that that information is out, let's get down to the real thing.
So, how is it? Is it cold?
No, it's cold. Hot? Cold?
It's cold. Oh, I see. Thank you very much.
I don't have anything to say. I didn't have anything to say.
Is it cold? Yes, it's cold. It's cold at night.
Let's go to the restaurant.
Today is December 8.
I told you yesterday that tomorrow is fresh pasta day.
I told you yesterday that tomorrow is Fresh Pasta Day, so it's important to be aware of it.
So tomorrow, the 8th, we'll finish what we've been talking about.
I'm going to say, "This is the end of this year. I think that people who work in agriculture are still not aware of this. I think it's still the same for farmers, who take a break after making crops, and then start the year's events again on February 8, the beginning of the new year.
There is also "Koto-hajime," or the beginning of the koto (the first day of the koto season).
Koto sakame. How was this year?
How was your year? Well, it's not over yet.
How was it? Well, it changed a lot.
I've changed, right?
Myself.
Until then, I had been like this for a long time.
I was like this all the time.
Scratching, scratching, scratching with one hand.
Like a DJ.
But I really changed.
I've been able to do shows and things like that,
I was even allowed to do the uterine ceremony.
In Hamashita.
That was in early spring, wasn't it?
It was a year of gekidō, with musicals and so on.
But for me personally, it was a very peaceful year.
It was what everyone calls an ordinary year, which is also a miracle. Yes, yes, yes. I always feel like something happens every year, or I feel like I'm in trouble. What is this? Something like this happens every year.
It happens a lot in comic books. I was able to spend my time peacefully, and I felt that I had grown up enough to be able to think peacefully.
It was a fresh year for me in a way. So you had a lot of troubles until the previous year, right?
I had been in a lot of trouble the year before, but this year, as well as for me, you all had a lot of trouble.
It's been a while since the Corona disaster has been cleared up, and I feel like I'm back to a normal life again.
Yes, there is, especially recently, because there are a lot of companies around the ship, you know, because of the Corona disaster
The company employees went home right away, so there was no one around at night. I can hear that weird karaoke coming from somewhere.
I don't know who's singing, but the notes are totally out of tune.
It's like everyday life is back... I thought, "Wow! It's been a year like that for me.
I had a lot of physical problems.
I had to go to the doctor more times than ever this year.
I've been going to the doctor more times than ever this year... but I've learned from it all... and I'm trying to improve.
So, to wrap things up, let's hear from you.
May I? This week, we've got a lot of letters.
Well, first of all, a little Japanese confectionery, or dango, or something like that, but they sent me something interesting.
I went shopping at a supermarket the other day, and I saw some ikinari dumplings, a Kumamoto specialty, on sale, so I bought them without hesitation because I missed them so much!
I used to go to Kumamoto once a year for motorcycle touring and buy them at a roadside station.
I was wondering if there is anything that you always eat or buy when you go to this prefecture or place, and I heard that the ikkinari dumplings look like this.
I didn't know about this one, so I looked it up and found that it has something like a sweet potato cut into squares written on it, and the reason why it's called ikinari-dango is because it's much easier to make than regular dango.
It doesn't take much time, so when you have guests over, you can serve them right away.
The name "ikinari dango" has remained unchanged, and it's still called ikinari dango.
I think it's pretty good, isn't it?
When it's getting colder, do you look up at the night sky?
Yes, I do.
I want it. - No, you want it.
I didn't start to say something really bad... and I thought it was bad...
I thought this during the live broadcast.
And especially in the fall and winter, when it gets colder, you can see them, right?
In the summer, it's warmer, so it's a little bit fuzzy.
So McMahon from Yokohama sent me this... he says you can take beautiful pictures of the starry sky with an iPhone.
May I? This is how he took this picture.
Isn't this Orion? Yes, it's me. Orion.
If you combine it with the star chart, you can get a clear image of Orion, like this.
Orion constellation... Orion constellation...
Look, this is my iphone, right?
The starry sky is like the beginning of Star Wars.
If you combine this with the number of constellations, this is exactly how it happened!
Right?
It's probably a big triangle... like Sirius...
I can't believe how beautiful it looks!
The iPhone is amazing!
Well, well, well, well. It's evolving.
And, uh... well, anyway...
There's a lot of pictures. They're here. Oh, my God, it's wonderful!
Hamamatsu City, Shizuoka Prefecture.
He often sends me his drawings, and he let me draw the master!
So, here it is.
Wow! It's great!
This is the way a good artist draws.
And it's all in blue, but you can tell it's not a bad drawing.
Who's this guy? He's so cool.
Is it me? Me? Me?
Thank you!
It's stylized.
Stylish.
Well, that's how Mineral sees you.
Thank you very much.
And here's another nice picture of Mr. Pell, high school student in Yokohama, who probably really likes photography.
He sends me pictures of beautiful everyday scenery, but it's the sky in an ordinary alley in an ordinary residential area.
Telegraph poles and power lines... a typical Japanese landscape in a sense.
It's like Eva!
Eva, indeed! The Third Tokyo, the Third Master! Cool! Cool!
It's true that in other countries, there are no such things as telegraph poles.
They're all buried underground. It's a very unique Japanese style.
I've never been to all of them. I've never been to Europe or anything like that.
Not at all.
I don't know...
Wow, it's really nice.
It changes so much depending on how you look at it.
That's true.
Telegraph poles... when you look at them closely...
There's something amazing on it.
Like this...
It's huge!
Like a transformer
It's like, wow!
You don't get to see it that often.
Also... it's nice...
Oh, this picture is good, too... Panda in distress
Thank you very much. Pandas often send us their wonderful drawings.
Pocky Day was held on November 11 at a place called "What's today's day?
He sent me a picture of them, and I drew them as brothers, Rhea and Subie.
I drew a picture of Mr. Rhea, who looks like a brother, and Subie, who looks like a sister, and it was like this.
So, now that that's out of the way, I'm going to end the distribution soon... but I hope you all enjoyed it. No, it's just that there are no earthquakes, so they can put it in the lower part of the building.
I see... I see...
I didn't know that.
I didn't know that about Europe.
I heard that Europe doesn't have earthquakes at all.
Is that so?
Yeah.
Japan is overlapped by plates.
Volcanoes are close to volcanoes.
So there are hot springs instead.
I see. That's a good thing.
So, there are hot springs, and they're close to each other.
There are four seasons.
I see.
Yes, so of course we don't like earthquakes and so on, but...
But it's also very close to our lives.
I see.
That's why Japan is such a miraculous country.
So, if the sea disappears...
Japan is like this now, isn't it?
Fuji is the highest peak.
Fuji is at the top of the volcano.
If the sea disappears, Tokyo will be located in the middle of the mountains.
So Tokyo Bay will be on top of the mountains.
So Tokyo Bay is just going to be on top of it like a big mountain.
I see... it's miraculous.
I want to be moved... but there's something else, Master... can you stop making that gag face? You know... you make funny faces when you eat dumpling buns, don't you?
It's not a funny face. It's not a funny face. It's not my original face.
It's not original, but it's a reaction.
So, everyone, New Year's Eve delivery, and also the Daikanai Devil.
And also the Daikanai Devil and many more exciting events to look forward to, so please look forward to them.
Thank you very much!
If you don't see a musician, you're either waiting for me, or you have an aura of waiting for me, guys.
See you all at 8pm this week!